next day at the service center
see guys
how it's damaged
[Music]
[Applause]
hello friends come on
today i am going to bring to you another
video and this time i will be sharing my
experience on what i had to face with
renault roadside assistance when i had
an accident with my tiger back in june
in my last video i told you guys that
because of this wagonr not using any
turn signals and taking a sudden turn
the front right tire bumped into the
divider and the car's wheel axle got
damaged
this incident happened near shilparam
madhapur
i had my son with me in the car and it
was a harrowing experience for both of
us
thankfully we were not hurt
now my wife came to the accident spot
and took my son home
after that it was one of the worst
experiences i had dealing with renault
roadside assistance
i called their helpline number and after
taking all the necessary details they
told me that the tow truck would come
soon
now kyger is my first car and i never
had experienced such kind of breakdown
based on which it had to be towed
hence i did not know that there were two
kinds of tow trucks
one which ties a rope at the front or
back bumper of the car and drags it away
and another one which lifts the car
completely on the truck
when finally the tow truck came to take
my car to the nearest service center it
was the kind which lifts the car
completely on its back when they tried
moving my tiger they could not because
the front right tyre bent backwards and
got stuck into the mud guard initially
after the accident i somehow managed to
move the car very slowly to the side of
the road but after that we could not
move the car any further
hence the first tow truck to the
accident spot was of no use since the
car had to be moved and lifted to the
back of the truck
those folks who came in that tow truck
called the driver of another tow truck
which could put a rope in the front
bumper of the car and drag it to the
service center
the other truck said they were in second
rabad and it would take a couple of
hours for them to reach the spot
evidently renault roadside assistance
only has two trucks in total for the
hyderabad area
i had no other choice but to wait in the
meantime there was a person from the
roadside assistance customer care who
kept calling me in between and kept me
updated on the progress
after some time he also stopped
communicating
i received no further updates from his
site i was only getting a few automated
messages that a case was registered with
them
and that the tow truck would come soon
the messages had the location of the tow
truck but it was of no use since it was
not a real-time data and however times i
checked their location
it showed that the tow truck hasn't
moved
the accident happened at around 6 pm in
the evening
the first truck came at 7 pm or so after
that i waited for almost three hours and
each time i talked with someone from the
customer care
they said that the truck will be there
soon
it was almost 10 pm in the night and i
was stranded there all alone i finally
asked one of their executives to send
someone to at least collect the car keys
and then that person can stay there and
coordinate to bring my car to the
nearest service center
it even started to rain heavily around 9
30 pm and i had to take shelter inside a
bus stop
finally at 10 30 pm someone came from
their team and took the car keys after
which they tried to book a cab for me to
go home
you guys know how it is with ola and
uber nowadays in hyderabad the cabs kept
cancelling since the roadside assistance
folks would pay them with ola money or
something
finally i had to book a cab myself and i
went home
i gave them the cab receipt and after
more than a week and multiple following
i received a refund in my paytm wallet
for the amount that i paid to the cab
that night
next day i received confirmation that
the car was finally taken to the service
center at around 2 am in the morning
i took a wise decision to come back home
else god knows how much longer i had to
wait
i just pray that my kyger never breaks
down on the road and i don't have to
experience another renault roadside
assistance saga in my life the service
was pathetic
if you are a renault car owner please
share your experiences of roadside
assistance down in the comment section
below
thank you for watching
and see you guys soon